socividz.com 2015-11-06

# SociVidz

**PRIVACY POLICY**

SociVidz.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. Period.

How we gather information from users

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site. Like most Web sites, SociVidz.com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.

What we do with the information we collect

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on SociVidz.com to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by SociVidz.com and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by SociVidz.com may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of ecommerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements

SociVidz.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a SociVidz.com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through SociVidz.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. SociVidz.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. SociVidz.com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of SociVidz.com and this policy.

Children

SociVidz.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe SociVidz.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at support (*at/] SociVidz.com - replace ' (*at/] ' with @

Changes to this Policy

SociVidz.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

Disclaimer - Compensation and Affiliate

The purpose of this section is to establish any compensatory affiliation with numerous companies whose products are being promoted on this site.

SociVidz.com is affiliated with numerous companies whose products are being promoted on this site, as a

Marketing Affiliate and receives compensation for sales of numerous products and services found on this site, generated through promotions and therefore has an established connection with numerous companies whose products are being promoted on this site that might lead some readers to believe that the SociVidz.com review of numerous products and services found on this site is biased. However, the review and comments on this page are to the best of our knowledge the true statements and beliefs of SociVidz.com.

SociVidz.com often receives compensation in the form of free promotional products or cash or cash equivalent for the purposes of reviewing numerous products and services found on this site, for numerous companies whose products are being promoted on this site.

EARNINGS DISCLAIMER AND FORWARD LOOKING STATEMENTS

Every effort has been made to accurately represent numerous products and services found on this site and it’s potential. However, there is no guarantee that you will earn any money using numerous products and services found on this site, the techniques or ideas in these materials. Examples in these materials are not to be interpreted as a promise or guarantee of earnings in any way. Earning potential is entirely dependent on the person using these products, ideas and techniques and we do not purport this as a “get rich scheme.”

Your level of success in attaining the results claimed in our materials depends on the time you devote to the program, ideas and techniques mentioned, your finances, previous knowledge and various skills.

Since these factors differ according to individuals, we cannot guarantee your success or income level. Nor are we responsible for any of your actions.

Materials in the product and on our website may contain information that includes or is based upon forward-looking statements within the meaning of the Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Forward-Looking Statements give our expectations or forecasts of future events. You can identify these statements by the fact that they do not relate strictly to historical or current facts. Such Forward Looking Statements use words such as “anticipate,” “estimate,” “expect,” “project,” “intend,” “plan,” “believe,” and other such words and terms of similar meaning in connection with a description of potential earnings or financial performance. Your Results May Vary from ours and those of anyone else who is, or will be using these products, techniques, and/or services.

Any and all forward looking statements here or on any of our sales material are intended to express our opinion of earnings potential not actual earnings expected. Many factors will be important in determining your actual results and no guarantees are made, expressed or implied that you will achieve results similar to ours or anybody else’s. In fact no guarantees are made that you will achieve any results from our ideas and techniques in our material at all. All materials on this site are © copyrighted by SociVidz.com. No part of this may be copied, or changed in any format, sold, or used in any way, online or offline, other than what is outlined within this site, under any circumstances without express permission from SociVidz.com

DMCA Disclaimer

SociVidz.com respects the intellectual property of others. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please follow our Notice and Procedures for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement below.

Notice and Procedure for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement Pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.

If you believe that you hold a claim of copyright infringement against SociVidz.com, submit notice of your claim to the following Designated Agent:

Service Provider: SociVidz.com

Email Address to Which Notification Should Be Sent: support (*at/] SociVidz.com - replace ' (*at/] ' with @

To be effective, the notification of your claim of copyright infringement should be written and should include the following:

A statement that you are the owner of the exclusive right you claim has been infringed, or a statement that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that has allegedly been infringed.

A statement, under penalty of perjury, that the information in the notification is accurate. Your signature. (The signature may be electronic.)

The identification of the copyrighted work you claim has been infringed. (If you claim that multiple copyrighted works have been infringed you can submit one notification with a list of the allegedly infringed works.)

Identification of the material that you claim to be infringing and information reasonably sufficient to permit SociVidz.com to locate the material.

Information reasonably sufficient to permit SociVidz.com to contact you, including your address, telephone number, fax number and, if available, an electronic mail address.

You can provide contact information for the owner of the exclusive right that you claim has been infringed if you are not the owner, but rather authorized to act on behalf of the owner.

A statement you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.

SociVidz.com will respond to any DMCA complaints in a timely manner. Should you be the copyright holder of a specific piece of content featured on this site without your permission, SociVidz.com will remove it in a timely manner once notified.
